get up!
i don't know shout it
Dreaming on!
Whoa!
Have I made myself clear, Paddle Spaddle?
I decided on this alliance myself.
It is not your place to disapprove.
I'm concerned, Mama.
Just wary of anything
that might jeopardize
your chances of becoming
King of the Pirates.
you think i'm stupid enough to walk
into a trap have some faith unless i've
lost the trust of my own family of
course not my concerns were unfounded
well that's that a shame Patty
Speed it looks like our short-lived
partnership has come to an end already
lickety split i suppose we're back to
being enemies.
Marco, I thought you
were better than this.
Why are you siding with those young
punks?
So much for Whitebeard's legacy, if
the remnants have all lost their way.
I don't see
myself as a remnant, and I
doubt the others do as well.
You're clueless.
Pops will never be forgotten.
But his voice and his dreams
don't bind us one bit.
Those who were left behind are free.
I think that's just what he'd want.
I see.
Dead men give no orders.
Do as you will, then.
I don't expect you to get it.
That's fine.
I'll show you what freedom looks like!
So it's him.
Carrot!
Where are you going?
I have to get revenge for Pedro!
We've got this!
You keep moving!
Thanks, guys!
Quite the ruckus out there.
At least no one is bothering us.
But it's so lonely without guests.
Big Sis Maria, would you sing us a song?
But of course.
And I think you'll like this one.
A snowy night bathed in white.
Come back!
Long they've waited, their love ill-fated
Yearning for a tender gaze
Searching through the winter haze
Then at last, robed in moonlight
Together again their hearts take
flight Oh, it's so romantic!
Their passions
Oh, Ignite!
I'm not the one who's dying today.
And we come!
What the hell?
I can't believe I saw even a
shadow of Odin in you fools.
The way you toss his name
around is an embarrassment.
All you did was hide beneath his
wing, pretending to be samurai.
But the game is over now.
You want to find out
if we were pretending?
You'll find your answer
at the tip of this blade!
Well spoken. Let's begin. Now!
Crimson Cat Dance!
Top of style!
River of sea!
What?
Canine!
Falling snow sites!
Slicing round!
Their attacks have nothing like Odin's.
They don't possess even a
fraction of his strength.
How are they able to harm me?
Dawn!
This is it!
Face me!
Perish!
Nope!
Scrolling Jutsu!
My scroll keep hours off!
Give me your words!
Oh.
Now I return it your own
fight blast with restoration.
You think you have the power to kill me?
Letting an old Shatter does not
impart you with its strength.
He lifted you up, but now you fall!
It's true.
We liked conviction of our own.
Your two-sword style lesson begins today!
We'll pass, thanks.
We each have our own sword styles,
and we're keeping it that way.
But it's my secret technique!
It's powerful, too!
You really don't want to learn it?
Of course we wanted to learn,
but each one of us also yearned
to be his foremost disciple.
If we had competed for that position,
it would have been a terrible battle,
fraught with bloodshed.
This is how great our love for him was.
Odin!
Two-sword style!
What the hell are you doing?
This isn't a game!
You words!
I'll teach you about you, O2.
What do you say?
Get back here!
We uphold our swords
and our spirits alike to
rescue the land of Wado
from your wicked clutches!
Face my flame red!
Kaido, make light of my
samurai at your own peril.
People will speak of your heroic
death for generations to come.
They can call me a hero or a fool.
They can even forget me,
but my spirit will live on!
Oden Two-Sword style!
Prince Totsuka!
Keep eating! Keep drinking!
Once tomorrow comes, it'll all be gone!
The Flower Capital is the only place in
the land of Wano where people can prosper.
And yet, like the rest of the nation,
the hearts of the citizens
here are filled with fear,
and a great unease hides
behind their smiles.
Someday, the Kozuki samurai will
return, they tell themselves.
They will save this country.
This is a legend that unites the nation.
All people, rich or poor, hold it in
their heart, so that they may carry on.
Ah, that's good, but it hits this
old man hard, I gotta tell ya.
All that stress just melts away.
Yes, it really feels
just like the old days.
I wish we could go back.
That sure would be fine.
Or I wish today would never end.
Sure is refreshing, huh?
I've never had water that
didn't burn my throat before.
Goodness, what a wonderful day.
Even the air is fresh and clean.
Breathe it all in.
The festival won't last forever.
This is the last drink
I'll get for a while.
Then it's a whole year of dry times.
That bastard!
As long as Kaido's here,
there's no winning this.
At least no one's getting killed today.
Hey, I'll drink to that any old time.
Once Orochi's back might even be
my head on the chopping block.
Did you hear the news?
The Kozuki clan's back
and they're probably out
there fighting for their
lives right about now.
Don't know if I'd buy
it, but that sounds fun.
Mind telling me the rest of the story?
Hell yeah! Get this!
The samurai brought back powerful
warriors from all over the world.
Then they took them to Onigashima
to give Kaido and Orochi a beating.
And soon, we'll be free!
That's one hell of a tall tale, my friend,
but you're alive to dream for today!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Oh, yeah!
Anymore!
Bear!
Aaaaaah! Aaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Don't go!
Somebody! Aaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Damn it!
Don't go anywhere near them!
Pull back for now!
It's not safe! Stay away!
They're all samurai, aren't they?
Why are they splitting up?
I'm guessing this is the plague.
This disease is incredibly infectious.
I can't believe it spread so easily.
This is not what medical
science should be used for!
You're the real Oni Queen!
The lick seal off the exits to
the other floors now nothing,
but dead men walking in here.
Seems like my masterpiece is a big
hit playgrounds boys ice only style.
I don't have time for you!
You think I'm just gonna roll over?
I said back off, bastard!
Just cool it a sec.
We don't have time!
All this is pointless
if you can't beat Kaido.
So save your strength, okay?
I bet we'll get promoted if
we take Straw Hat's hand!
Hey, hell yeah!
Take out Fancy Browse first!
Let's do it!
I'll finish you all in one shot.
You idiots have no idea
what you're in for.
Party table kick course!
how dare you you're gonna pay for
treating my men like that you punks
aren't taking another step prepare
yourselves cuz I'm gonna wreck ya
is that a arm gorilla that's
messed up what you got
something to say all right If I
don't like my gorilla harm, wise guy!
Then where should the gorilla be?
I don't know!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Not bad.
This guy's pretty damn tough.
He punches and the gorilla punches too?
What a suck!
Chibi, you made it!
I had a feeling this is
where I would find you.
Our enemies are persistent.
Uh, Briscola, sir?
Are you still alive?
No.
Oh, no.
Wake up, man.
Hang in there.
Hey, blue guy, that was cheap,
Attacking a man straight in the back.
Okay, you gotta let me
fight him this time.
What did I tell you?
I'll take care of this.
Just chill out and save
your energy for Kaido.
There are tons of them.
It'll take you forever to beat them all.
Shut up.
I'll do it in ten seconds.
Watch me.
Just stay here. Too slow.
I bet we could do it in three.
Hey, you two are supposed
to be fighting me.
Pay attention.
I'm ready for round two.
Tastes by Gorilla Punchbowl!
That's enough of that!
Fishman Karate! Shark breakfast!
General Briscola!
Great, it's settled.
All right, T-bay!
Luffy, I'll escort you
to the rooftop myself.
No more fighting until we get there.
You need to save your energy.
Hey, that's exactly what I just said.
I've got this under control.
We made it this far, didn't we?
Oh, pardon me. My mistake.
Luffy, our samurai allies must be
fighting for their lives right now.
We should aid them quickly.
Yeah!
Let's do this!
How did you talk him into it so easily?
You're gonna pay for what
you did to General Briscola!
Kill them all, man!
As you can see, Luffy fights
whenever he gets a chance.
Let's keep an eye out.
Wait for me!
What did you see, Bahouan?
Well, Yamato and Momonosuke are
running through the Ripe Brain Tower.
They should be outside soon.
Good enough for me.
This is key.
We now know the identities of those
imbeciles who crashed the banquet.
They have roughly 5,400 soldiers.
soldiers most of them seem to be samurai,
their forces are led by odin's retainers.
their objective is clear:
this is a plot to restore the kozuki
clans of power to transform the nation.
in other words,
they want to make odin's son kozuki
momonosuke the shogun of the land of wano!
No, all gifters in Tobiropo who are not
locked in combat, you have a new mission.
Kozuki Momonosuke is currently
in the right brain tower.
Find him and bring his head to me.
That'll take all the
fight out of the samurai.
As for the pirates, that's another matter.
Don't worry, we'll deal with
them when the time comes.
He told us to kill him
instead of catching him alive.
This should be easy.
Now fire!
Go!
Collect the corpse! Yes, sir!
I should be here.
Wait, what's that?
Uh, the barrel?
Huh? Huh?
Just a knife?
Against the Armored Division?
Don't make me laugh!
Shirabu!
I'll be fine.
Stay hidden, my lord.
You're brave, at least.
But as their name implies, everyone
on my team has armored bodies.
You're out of options.
Aim for the brat!
I'll protect you!
Please, run away...
Shinobu?
I'll kill you both!
Right here, right now!
That tiny weapon won't be enough!
Dawn, no!
Please run away, Lord Momonosuke!
Run away?
Is that right?
Is that what a Shogun is supposed to do?
Run, Shinobu!
Don't die!
Little rat!
Stop it!
No!
Well, this is interesting.
You sure you want to butt
in, young master Yamato?
Who's butting in?
It's only natural that I would
fight for the Kozuki clan.
I am Odin, after all!
Aim those swords at his throat!
No celebrating until we know that
bastard is dead! Right you are!
Time to execute Kaido! Forward!
It was only a shadow, but I sensed the
strength of Kozuki Oden in your attack.
It would have been a fine time to die.
My scar aches again, and just like
always, I remember that fateful day.
Mother!
Help me!
Turn around!
He's hurting me!
If she hadn't meddled in that single
moment, that might have been the end.
But even with your strength
combined, you're still no Odin.
ROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROROR
But you won't reopen my scar
with such shallow attacks.
There's no hope for you.
A storm of slashes!
Ha!
Kiku!